<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<update xmlns="http://ns.adobe.com/air/framework/update/description/2.5">
	<versionNumber>1.4.0</versionNumber>
	<url>https://raw.github.com/jvanoostveen/Flash-Player-Switcher/master/release/FlashPlayerSwitcher.air</url>
	<description><![CDATA[Changelog

v1.4.0
- Ability to change Flash Player names.
- In making the internet a better place, all analytics tracking has been removed. 

v1.3.1
- Added more Growl notifications.
- Containing directory is now also deleted when deleting plugins from the storage.

v1.3.0
- Growl (v1.3) notifications added (issue #17).
- Improved Alert handling (issue #18).

v1.2.2
- Layout fix when having no active Flash Player plugin (issue #19).
- Now checks system installed plugin after activating app as well.
- Updated the Help.

v1.2.1
- Fixed DockIcon menu version info when no user plugin was installed.
- Show system player version when no user plugin is installed (issue #16).

v1.2.0
- Fixed storing plugins with a custom storage path.
- Compacted listing of stored plugins by grouping release and debugger based on version.
- Ability to select and download multiple plugins in one go.
- Added localization (English and Dutch for the moment, awaiting more translations).
- Ability to disable editing of storage (useful for managed storage).
- Ability to activate a plugin from the Dock icon.
- New application icon (by Igor van Oostveen).
- Added FDT5 logo and link as Powerflasher sponsered a FDT5 Max license :).

v1.1.0
- Storage location for database and plugins can now be chosen.
- Better positioning of Help window.
- Text changes.
- Added Help menu with links to the help and issue list.
- Rechecks installed versions when application is activated.

v1.0.1
- Multiple Help windows issue fixed.

v1.0.0
- All basic stuff is in.
- Help added.
- Added alert when removing user plugin.

v0.9.1
- Download progress when adding plugins.
- Visual feedback in downloadable plugin list.

v0.9.0
- Added ability to download plugins into the storage.
  (visuals like progres bars etc aren't in yet)

v0.8.5
- Added an alert when deleting a plugin from the storage.
- Added an alert after installing a plugin.

v0.8.4
- Added ability to delete installed plugins.

v0.8.3
- First public release.]]></description>
</update>